doc2pdf.com 2017-02-25

# DOC2PDF - Privacy Policy & Terms of Service

By using our services, you agree to comply with the terms of service and be bound by the privacy policy herein.

## Changes to the Policy

If there are changes made to our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change(s) coming into effect.

## Your files

Most of the services offered by us require you to upload a copy of one or more files to our server where they are processed. Files uploaded by you and any copies produced while processing them are temporarily stored for your convenience and not made available to anyone else. We do not store any of the content in your files. Files are automatically deleted daily from our server.

## Use of Your Personal Information

To fulfill your transaction requests, you must allow us to use your personal information to identify you as a client. If you make a purchase or a donation via PayPal, we also receive some personal information about you and store your name and email address. We may send you service-related emails as a result of this transaction.

## Information Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. We will retain and use your information as necessary to provide you services and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Cookies and Other Web Technologies

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by our company and our partners, analytics, or service providers. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. This data is collected for internal analytical purposes in order to provide better services and to respond to any questions you may have after using our services.

Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you with advertising based on your browsing activities and interests.

## Security, Intrusion, and Detection

For website security purposes, and to ensure that our website remains available to all visitors, all network traffic is monitored in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, cause damage, or conduct criminal activity. To protect the system from unauthorized use and to ensure that the system is functioning properly, individuals accessing our website are subject to monitoring. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under applicable law.

## Links to Third-Party Sites

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from this one. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

## Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and widgets, as well as the “Share this” button and all interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page(s) you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## No Warranties

We strive to provide a service that works efficiently and without errors, and to provide support via email should you need it. However, any services provided on this website are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. We do not guarantee their availability, accuracy, completeness, or the availability of support related to them. We may add, remove, or change the services provided without notice.

## Limitation of Our Liability

Your use of this website is at your own risk. Under no circumstances shall **DOC2PDF LTD** , its suppliers, or any other party involved in creating, producing, or delivering this website's contents or services be liable to you or any other person for any indirect, direct, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising from your access to, or use of, this website.

## Regarding Copyrights

Many files are copyrighted works of others. Please respect that. Any use of our services for purposes that infringe on a copyright is prohibited. It is your responsibility to know whether you are doing so. In general, unless you are the owner of a file or have been granted a legal right to modify a file, you should not use our services to do so. Also, unless you are the owner of a file, do not distribute a copy of a file from which you have removed any kind of protection.

## Automated Use

This website is meant to be used by human visitors. Any kind of automated use of this website without a written consent from **DOC2PDF LTD** is prohibited. Such use is subject to being blocked without notice. 

The services on this website are offered by **DOC2PDF LTD** , a company located at **Chestney House, 149 Market Street, ST ANDREWS, Fife KY16 9PF, United Kingdom**.

You are welcome to contact us at [info@doc2pdf.com](mailto:info@doc2pdf.com) with any questions or concerns.

Last updated on **2016-04-27**
